Facilities Management Department fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Concordia Management, 1974 - 1980; F-11-4; 2.51 m of textual records
  - Mechanical Work (CB-05.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-94)
  - Mechanical Installations Co. Ltd. Part A (CB-05.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-94)
  - Mechanical installations Co. Ltd. Part B (CB-05.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-95)
  - Millwork and Electrical Specs (CB-06), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-95)
  - Electrical Services: SFU, MPX Hume and Rumble (CB-06), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-95)
  - Electrical Services (CB-06.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-95)
  - Commonwealth Construction Ltd. Electrical Division Hume and Rumble (CB-06.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-95)
  - Damproofing (CB-07.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Coast Hudson Ltd. (CB-07.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Roofing and Waterproofing (CB-08.1), 1976 - 1977; F-11-4-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Coast Hudson Ltd. (CB-08.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Hollow Metal Doors and Frames (CB-09), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Hollow Metal doors and Frames (CB-09-B), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Campbell and Grill Ltd. (CB-09B.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Sandblasting Architectural concrete (CB-10.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Seymour Painting Ltd. (CB-10.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-96)
  - Windows, Entrances, and Skylights (CB-11), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 11-97)
  - Contrax Glass and Metal Ltd. (CB-11.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 11-97)
  - Miscellaneous Metal (CB-13.1), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-97)
  - Alpine Steel Ltd. (CB-13.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-97)
  - Pre-Cast Concrete (CB-14.1), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-97)
  - Bordignon Construction Ltd. (CB-14.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 11-97)
  - Toilet Compartment (CB-15.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 11-97)
  - SW Fleming and Co. Ltd. (CB-15.2), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 11-97)
  - Masonry (CB-16.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 11-98)
  - Fred Lutje Masonry Ltd. (CB-16.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 11-98)
  - Folding Doors (CB-17.1), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 11-98)
  - Stanley - Bumeda Ltd. (CB-17.2), 1978 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 11-98)
  - Rough and Finish Carpentry (CB-18.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 11-98)
  - Ratcliff and Sons Construction Co. Ltd. (CB-18.2), 1978 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 11-98)
  - Overhead Doors (CB-20.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 11-99)
  - Michael Zagorsky Ltd. (CB-20.2), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 11-99)
  - Millwork (CB-21), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 11-99)
  - Bel-Par Industries (CB-21.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 11-99)
  - Drywall and Ceiling (CB-22.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 11-99)
  - Alpine Drywall (CB-22.2), 1978 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 11-100)
  - Ceramic Tile (CB-23.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 11-100)
  - Metro Tile Co. Ltd. (CB-23.2), 1978 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 11-100)
  - Resilient Flooring (CB-25.1), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 11-100)
  - Fred M. Beatty Ltd. (CB-25.2), 1978 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 11-100)
  - Tom G. Dinesan Landscaping (CB-31.2), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 11-100)
  - Tom G. Dinesan Landscaping Ltd. Work orders (CB-31.3), 1979; F-11-4-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 11-100)
  - Site Work (CB-32.1), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 11-100)
  - Smith Brothers and Wilson Ltd. (CB-32.2), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Hardwood Gym Floor (CB-36.1), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - BC Hardwood Floor (CB-36.2), 1978 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Air and Water Balancing (CB-37.1), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - KD Engineering Ltd. (CB-37.02), 1979; F-11-4-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Project Documentation Guidelines (CB-11.3), F-11-4-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Memos to all Contractors (CB-11.4), F-11-4-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Correspondence - General (CB-11.9), F-11-4-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Finish Hardware (CB-12.1), F-11-4-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Newspaper Clippings (CB-12.2), F-11-4-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Press Releases and Tender Advertisements (CB-12.3), F-11-4-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Correspondence with Solicitor (CMCL) (CB-14.2), F-11-4-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 11-101)
  - Insurance - Policies (Project) (CB-15.1), F-11-4-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Insurance - Correspondence (Project) (CB-15.2), F-11-4-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Blue Flame Propane (Trailer Heating System) (CB-16.1), F-11-4-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Copying and Printing - General Info (CB-16.2), F-11-4-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Photographs (CB-16.3), F-11-4-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - TR Trades Reproductions Ltd. (CB-16.5), F-11-4-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Wilson Stationery (CB-16.6), F-11-4-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Xerox (CB-16.7), F-11-4-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - First Aid Trailer and Equipment (CB-16.8), F-11-4-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Progress Claims (CB-21.0), F-11-4-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Commitment Reports (CB-25), F-11-4-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Unions - Correspondence (CB-31), F-11-4-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - WCB (CB-35), F-11-4-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - Safety Reports (CB-35.1), F-11-4-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 11-102)
  - WCB - Inspection Reports (CB-35.2), F-11-4-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Falsework Design Drawings as per WCB (CB-35.3), F-11-4-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - First Aid Attendants Accident Records (CB-35.4), F-11-4-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Estimate Back-up (CB-40.2.1), 1975 - 1976; F-11-4-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Preliminary Budget Estimate (CB-40.2), F-11-4-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Official Estimate (CB-40.3), 1976; F-11-4-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Official Estimate (CB-40.3), F-11-4-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Trade Package Estimate (CB-40.4), F-11-4-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Cash Flow Assessments (CB-40.5), F-11-4-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Millwork - Budget Details (CB-40.6.2), F-11-4-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Budget Revisions (CB-40.6.1, 1975 - 1976; F-11-4-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Cost Studies Education Office Complex (CB-41.2), F-11-4-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 11-103)
  - Cost Studies Health Services Expansion (CB-41.3), F-11-4-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 11-104)
  - MPX Extension (CB-41.4), F-11-4-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 11-104)
  - Cost Studies Unfinished Areas (CB-41.5), F-11-4-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 11-104)
  - Cost Studies Landscaping (CB-41.6), F-11-4-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 11-104)
  - Building Specs (CB-45), F-11-4-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 11-104)
  - Project Schedules (CB-46), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 11-104)
  - Chronological File, 1977; F-11-4-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 11-104)
  - Hoarding, F-11-4-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 11-104)
  - Chronological CMCL Correspondence (CB-60) - Part A, 1977; F-11-4-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - Chronological CMCL Correspondence (CB-60) - Part B, 1977; F-11-4-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - Chronological CMCL Correspondence (CB-60), 1975 - 1977; F-11-4-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - Chronological CMCL Correspondence (CB-60) - Lists of Drawings (CB-60.2), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - Chronological CMCL Correspondence (CB-60) - Document Transmittal (Out-Going) (CB-60.1.1), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - Chronological CMCL Correspondence (CB-60) - Document Transmittal (In-Coming) (CB-60.1.2), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - Correspondence with Owner (CB-61.1) - Part A, 1975 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - Correspondence with Owner (CB-61.1) - Part B, 1975 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - Correspondence with Owner (CB-61.1), 1978 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 11-105)
  - SFU Monthly Progress Reports (CB-61.4), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 11-106)
  - SFU Recommendations - Trade (CB-61.5), F-11-4-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 11-106)
  - Daily Logs (CB-61.6), 1976; F-11-4-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 11-106)
  - Daily Logs (CB-61.6), Part A, 1977; F-11-4-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 11-106)
  - Daily Logs (CB-61.6), Part B, 1977; F-11-4-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 11-106)
  - Daily Logs (CB-61.6), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-119 (Archival box - standard 11-106)
  - Phase II Design Program (CB-62.1), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-120 (Archival box - standard 11-106)
  - Correspondence - Downs/Archambault (D/A) (62.1), 1975 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-121 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Correspondence - Downs/Archambault (D/A) (62.1), Part A, 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-122 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Correspondence - Downs/Archambault (D/A) (62.1), Part B, 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-123 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - D/A Architects - Job Inspection Reports (CB-62.2), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-124 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Architects Jobsite Instructions (CB-62.3), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-125 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - For Approval - Documents to Architect (CB-62.4), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-126 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Correspondence - Buch and Bohlam (CB-63.1), 1975 - 1977; F-11-4-0-0-127 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Bush and Bohlam Ltd. - Job Inspection Reports (CB-63.2), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-128 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Correspondence - Park and Djwa (CB-64.1), 1974 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-129 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Park and Djwa Engineering Co. - Job Inspection Reports (CB-64.2), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-130 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Keen Engineering (1972) Ltd. (CB-64.3), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-131 (Archival box - standard 11-107)
  - Correspondence - WT Haggert CB-(65.1), 1975 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-132 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - WT Haggert and Co. Ltd. - Job Inspection Reports (CB-65.2), 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-133 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Pour Slips (CB-66.0), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-134 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - G. Spratt and Assoc. Ltd. - Waterproofing Consultant (CB-69.2), 1977; F-11-4-0-0-135 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - D. Vaughan and Assoc. Ltd. - Landscaping Consultant (CB-69.3), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-136 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - G. Brawner and Assoc. Ltd. - Soil Consultant (CB-69.4), 1974 - 1977; F-11-4-0-0-137 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - Barnett Resource Surveys Ltd. (CB-69.5), (Land Surveyor), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-138 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - City of Burnaby (CB-70.3), 1975 - 1977; F-11-4-0-0-139 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - Weather Conditions (CB-70.6), 1975 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-140 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - Meetings with Owners (CB-80.1), 1975; F-11-4-0-0-141 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - Meeting - Individual Team Members (CB-80.2), 1975; F-11-4-0-0-142 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Correspondence - Meeting with Contractors - Job Site Meetings Part A (CB-80.5), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-143 (Archival box - standard 11-108)
  - Meetings (with Contractors) Part B, Job Site Meetings (CB-80.5), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-144 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Meetings - CMCL Internal (CB-80.6), 1975 - 1976; F-11-4-0-0-145 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Meetings - Safety Council, Part A (CB-80.7), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-146 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Meetings - Safety Council, Part B (CB-80.7), 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-147 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Meetings - Mechanical Progress (CB-80.8), 1978; F-11-4-0-0-148 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Arch./Struct. Sketches, 1976 - 1977; F-11-4-0-0-149 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Correspondence Between Architect and SFU, 1975; F-11-4-0-0-150 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Prosegger, 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-151 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Recommendations, SFU, 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-152 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Terra Engineering Labs Ltd., 1978; F-11-4-0-0-153 (Archival box - standard 11-109)
  - Classroom Complex: Field Orders, Part A, 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-154 (Archival box - standard 11-110)
  - Classroom Complex: Field Orders, Part B, 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-155 (Archival box - standard 11-110)
  - Classroom Complex: Field Orders, Part C, 1977 - 1978; F-11-4-0-0-156 (Archival box - standard 11-110)
  - Variation Orders, SFU, Part A, 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-157 (Archival box - standard 11-110)
  - Variation Orders, SFU, Part B, 1977 - 1979; F-11-4-0-0-158 (Archival box - standard 11-110)
  - Variation Orders, No. 61.3 (1-69), Part A, F-11-4-0-0-159 (Archival box - standard 11-110)
  - Variation Orders, No. 61.3 (1-69), Part B, F-11-4-0-0-160 (Archival box - standard 11-110)
  - Variation Orders, No. 61.3 (1-69), Part C, F-11-4-0-0-161 (Archival box - standard 11-111)
  - Variation Orders, No. 613 (70-128), Part A, F-11-4-0-0-162 (Archival box - standard 11-111)
  - Variation Orders, No. 613 (70-128), Part B, F-11-4-0-0-163 (Archival box - standard 11-111)
  - Variation Orders, No. 613 (70-128), Part C, F-11-4-0-0-164 (Archival box - standard 11-111)
  - Variation Orders, No. 3 (129-178), Part A, F-11-4-0-0-165 (Archival box - standard 11-111)
  - Variation Orders, No. 3 (129-178), Part B, F-11-4-0-0-166 (Archival box - standard 11-111)
  - Variation Orders, No. 3 (129-178), Part C, F-11-4-0-0-167 (Archival box - standard 11-111)
  - Variation Orders, No. 4 (179-206), Part A, F-11-4-0-0-168 (Archival box - standard 11-112)
  - Variation Orders, No. 4 (179-206), Part B, F-11-4-0-0-169 (Archival box - standard 11-112)
  - Variation Orders, No. 4 (179-206), Part C, F-11-4-0-0-170 (Archival box - standard 11-112)
  - Variation Orders, No. 5 (207-219), F-11-4-0-0-171 (Archival box - standard 11-112)
  - File Specs - General Conditions, Architectural and Structural, Part A, F-11-4-0-0-172 (Archival box - standard 11-112)
  - File Specs - General Conditions, Architectural and Structural, Part B, F-11-4-0-0-173 (Archival box - standard 11-112)
- Architectural design reports, maps, and plans, [196-] - 1996; F-11-5; 32 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the construction of buildings on campus. Records include bound design reports, university maps, maps from the City of Burnaby, and architectural plans and drawings.
  The arrangement for records in this series was provided by the archivist. The architectural plans have been grouped together by building/project. Files are arranged chronologically.
  Textual records; Architectural drawings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
  Some materials have been digitized and are available for offline delivery. See [sub-series 1](f-11-5-1) and [sub-series 3](f-11-5-3); consult the reference archivist for more information.
  A file list is available.
  - Design reports, 1963 - 1996; F-11-5-1; 1 cm of textual records
    [File 1](f-11-5-1-0-1) has been digitized and is available for offline delivery as a pdf (uuid: 3802e4cd-a4a5-4511-a756-294e64615dd1); consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - Report of the Board of Assessors - SFU Architectural Competition, 1963; F-11-5-1-0-1
      File has been digitized and is available for offline delivery as a pdf (uuid: 3802e4cd-a4a5-4511-a756-294e64615dd1); consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - Student Residence Study, 1980; F-11-5-1-0-2
    - Contract Drawings for Ring Road and Parking Lot Construction, 1981; F-11-5-1-0-3
    - SFU Development Plan Concept, 1996; F-11-5-1-0-4
  - Maps, 1963 - 1982; F-11-5-2; 2 cm of textual records
    - SFU Architectural Competition - maps and site photos, 1963; F-11-5-2-0-1 (Cabinet MC 42-04)
    - SFU Student Residence and Transportation Survey - map, 1967; F-11-5-2-0-2 (Cabinet MC 42-04)
    - SFU and City of Burnaby maps, 1977; F-11-5-2-0-3 (Cabinet MC 42-04)
    - Aerial photo of The Corporation of the District of Burnaby, 1982; F-11-5-2-0-4 (Cabinet MC 42-04)
  - Architectural plans and drawings, [196-] - 1988; F-11-5-3; 13 cm of textual records
    Textual records; Architectural drawings; Textual records in electronic form (digitized)
    Files 3, 4, 7, and 9 have been digitized and are available for offline delivery as jpgs (uuid: 35e078bd7-2bef-4b64-8ba7-3426c88fe974); consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - SFU Student Residences - drawings, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-1 (Cabinet MC 42-10)
    - SFU Gymnasium - Swimming Pool - drawing, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-2 (Cabinet MC 42-10)
    - SFU Transportation Centre - drawing, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-3 (Cabinet MC 42-10)
      File has been digitized and is available for offline delivery as jpg or tif (uuid: 35e078bd7-2bef-4b64-8ba7-3426c88fe974); consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - SFU Central Mall - drawing, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-4 (Cabinet MC 42-10)
      Architectural drawings; Textual records in electronic form (digitized)
    - SFU Science Complex - drawing, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-5 (Cabinet MC 42-10)
    - SFU Theatre - drawing, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-6
    - SFU Stage 1 - drawing, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-7
      Architectural drawings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    - SFU Site Aerial - drawing, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-8
    - SFU Building Aerial - drawing, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-9
    - Landscaping - architectural plans, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-10
    - Daycare Centre - architectural plans, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-11
    - Arena Complex - architectural plans, [196-]; F-11-5-3-0-12
    - SFU Science Complex - drawing, 1963; F-11-5-3-0-13
    - SFU Development Plans - architectural plans, 1963 - 1974; F-11-5-3-0-14
    - Science Complex - architectural plans, 1964 - 1975; F-11-5-3-0-15
    - Library - architectural plans, 1964 - 1988; F-11-5-3-0-16
    - Shell Gas Station - architectural plans, 1965 - 1966; F-11-5-3-0-17
    - SFU Looking North East - drawing, 1966; F-11-5-3-0-18
    - Academic Quadrangle - architectural plans, 1968 - 1982; F-11-5-3-0-19
    - SFU Faculty Club - drawing, 1971; F-11-5-3-0-20
    - Faculty Club private dining area - drawing, 1971; F-11-5-3-0-21
    - Faculty Club entry waiting area - drawing, 1971; F-11-5-3-0-22
    - Faculty Club main lounge - drawing, 1971; F-11-5-3-0-23
    - Physical Plant - architectural plans, 1972; F-11-5-3-0-24
    - Post Office - architectural plans, 1973; F-11-5-3-0-25
    - Animal Care Unit - architectural plans, 1974; F-11-5-3-0-26
    - Art Gallery - architectural plans, 1974; F-11-5-3-0-27
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - architectural plans, vol. 1, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-28
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - architectural plans, vol. 2, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-29
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - architectural plans, vol. 3, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-30
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - architectural plans, vol. 4, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-31
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - architectural plans, vol. 5, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-32
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - architectural plans, vol. 6, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-33
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - design specifications, vol. 7, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-116)
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - design specifications, vol. 8, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-116)
    - Classroom Block II (Multi Purpose Complex) - design specifications, vol. 9, 1975 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-116)
    - Theatre - architectural plans, 1976; F-11-5-3-0-37
    - Health Services - architectural plans, 1977; F-11-5-3-0-38
    - Building equipment and fixture plans, 1977 - 1978; F-11-5-3-0-39
    - SFU Building Floor Plans, 1980; F-11-5-3-0-40
    - Classroom Complex - architectural plans, 1982; F-11-5-3-0-41
    - West Mall Complex - architectural plans, 1982 - 1983; F-11-5-3-0-42